I was traveling in Hawaii and I was
there with my boyfriend him and I were
going to watch the sunset along up here
I looked over at my boyfriend and there
was a wave above his head next thing I
knew we were sliding down the Rocks I
just started screaming in pain and found
out there that I had indeed broken my
spine 22 years old and 130 000 in debt
that would have been the worst getting
the bills was a lot of money with the
airvac the ambulance rides but Manulife
immediately took over they were so
assuring that everything was going to be
okay I felt really thankful and safe in
knowing that I'd be covered prior to the
accident I was thinking at the time of
using credit card insurance however I
liked Manulife better they cover
everything that I needed I'm doing good
now I'm not in debt I'm happy there's no
limits to what I want it is far easier
to go on vacation worry free and maybe
you don't get into an accident and if
you do then at least you're reassured
knowing that everything's gonna be taken
care of I will always pack Travel
Insurance yeah
[Music]